Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Miller, Dayton C. (Box-folder 70/3)
  - Miller, Mary (Mrs. Adolph C. Miller) (Box-folder 70/4)
  - Miller, Rosalie (Box-folder 70/5)
  - Millikan, Robert A. and Mrs. see California Institute of Technology
  - Mills College (miscellany), probably pre-1933 see also Milhaud, Darius and Coleman, Persis (Box-folder 70/6)
  - Mills College (miscellany) (Box-folder 70/7)
  - Mills College. Reinhardt, Aurelia Henry, 1927-1932 (Box-folder 70/8)
  - Mills College. Reinhardt, Aurelia Henry, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 70/9)
  - Mills College. Reinhardt, Aurelia Henry, undated (Box-folder 70/10)
  - Mills College. White, Lynn (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Milne, James A. (Box-folder 70/12)
  - "Min" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 70/13)
  - Miner, Antonia Sawyer see Sawyer, Antonia
  - Minghella, Aida (Box-folder 70/14)
  - Minneapolis Symphony String Quartet (Box-folder 70/15)
  - Minnetti, Giulio (Box-folder 70/16)
  - Minot, George R. (doctor) (Box-folder 70/17)
  - Miquelle, Renée Longy (Box-folder 70/18)
  - Mirovitch, Alfred (Box-folder 70/19)
  - Mischakoff, Mischa (Box-folder 70/20)
  - Missouri University see Quarles, James T.
  - Mitchell, Lucy Sprague and Wesley C., 1916-1928 (Box-folder 70/22)
  - Mitchell, Lucy Sprague and Wesley C., 1931-1953 (Box-folder 70/23)
  - Mitchell, Viola, 1934 (Box-folder 70/24)
  - Mitchell, Viola, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 70/25)
  - Mitchell, Viola, undated (Box-folder 70/26)
  - Mitropoulos, Dmitri (letter to) (Box-folder 70/21)
  - "Mo" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 70/27)
  - Modave, Jeanne (Box-folder 70/28)
  - Moe, Henry Allen see Guggenheim Foundation
  - Moeschinger, Albert (Box-folder 70/29)
  - Mohaupt, Richard (Box-folder 70/30)
  - Moiseiwitsch, Benno (Box-folder 70/31)
  - Moldavan, Nicolas and Belle, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 70/32)
  - Moldavan, Nicolas and Belle, 1939 (Box-folder 70/33)
  - Moldavan, Nicolas and Belle, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 70/34)
  - Moldavan, Nicolas and Belle, undated (Box-folder 70/35)
  - Molié, Denyse (Box-folder 70/36)
  - Molliére, Joseph (Box-folder 70/37)
  - Molnár, Ferenc (violist) and Marie, 1939 (Box-folder 70/38)
  - Molnár, Ferenc (violist) and Marie, 1940 (Box-folder 70/39)
  - Molnár, Ferenc (violist) and Marie, 1941-1953 (Box-folder 70/40)
  - Molnár, Ferenc (violist) and Marie, undated (Box-folder 70/41)
  - "Mon" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 71/1)
  - Moneak, Elena (Box-folder 71/2)
  - Monks, Jane B. (Box-folder 71/3)
  - Monnier, Madeleine (Box-folder 71/4)
  - Monroe, Harriet (Box-folder 71/5)
  - Montague, Gilbert H. (Box-folder 71/6)
  - Montalvo Foundation (Box-folder 71/7)
  - Monteux, Pierre (Box-folder 71/8)
  - Moody, Harriet (Box-folder 71/9)
  - Moog, Wilson T. see Smith College. Moog, Wilson T.
  - Moore, Benjamin (Box-folder 71/10)
  - Moore, Charles (Box-folder 71/11)
  - Moore, Douglas (Box-folder 71/12)
  - Moore, Eliza Coe (Mrs. Edward C. Moore) (Box-folder 71/13)
  - Moore, Elizabeth Evelyn (Box-folder 71/14)
  - Moore, Ernest C. (Box-folder 71/15)
  - Moore, Henry T. see Skidmore College
  - Moore, Mary Carr (Box-folder 71/16)
  - "Mor" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 71/17)
  - Moreau, Léon (Box-folder 71/18)
  - Morgenthau, Josie (Mrs. Henry Morgenthau) (Box-folder 71/19)
  - Mori, Rachele Maragliano see Maragliano-Mori, Rachele
  - Morini, Albert (Box-folder 71/20)
  - Moritz, Edvard (Box-folder 71/21)
  - Morize, André, Mrs. (Box-folder 71/22)
  - Morley, Rose (Box-folder 71/23)
  - Morris, Harold (Box-folder 71/24)
  - Morris, Ira Nelson, Mrs. (Box-folder 71/25)
  - Morrison, Anna Blake (Mrs. W.J. Morrison) (Box-folder 71/26)
  - Morros, Boris (Box-folder 71/27)
  - Morse, Henry W. (Box-folder 71/28)
  - Morse, Leila Livingston (letter to) (Box-folder 71/29)
  - Morton, Reah Sadowsky (Mrs. F. Rand Morton) (Box-folder 71/30)
  - "Mos" miscellaneous [NOTE: could not be located as of Sept. 2012] (Box-folder 71/31)
  - Moseley, Kate Williams (Box-folder 71/32)
  - Moses, Eugene (Box-folder 71/33)
  - Moses, Harriet R. (Box-folder 71/34)
  - Motion Picture Foundation (Box-folder 71/35)
  - Moton, Robert Russa see Tuskegee Institute
  - Motvani, K. L. (Box-folder 71/36)
  - Mount Holyoke College. Hammond, E.C. (Box-folder 71/37)
  - Mount Holyoke College. Leedy, Charles Denoe (Box-folder 71/38)
  - Mount Holyoke College (Box-folder 71/39)
  - Mount Holyoke Glee Club (Box-folder 71/40)
  - Moyse, Blanche Honegger (Box-folder 71/41)
  - "Mu" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 71/42)
  - Mukle, May (Box-folder 71/43)
  - Mumford, George S. (Box-folder 71/44)
  - Munch, Charles (Box-folder 71/45)
  - Murat, Ronald (Box-folder 71/46)
  - Murdock, Louise Hamilton (Box-folder 71/47)
  - Murdock, Kenneth B., Mrs. (Box-folder 71/48)
  - Murphy, Lenora (Box-folder 71/49)
  - "Mus" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 72/1)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston see Boston Museum of Fine Arts
  - Music Arts Society, Santa Monica (Box-folder 72/2)
  - Music for the Services (Box-folder 72/3)
  - Music Institute (Box-folder 72/4)
  - Music Library Association (Box-folder 72/5)
  - Music Press (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Music School Settlement (Box-folder 72/7)
  - Music Teachers National Association (Box-folder 72/8)
  - Musical America. Kramer, A. Walter (Box-folder 72/9)
  - Musical America (Box-folder 72/10)
  - Musical Courier (Box-folder 72/11)
  - Musicians' Club, London (Box-folder 72/12)
  - Musicians' Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy (Box-folder 72/13)
  - Musicians Foundation, N.Y. (Box-folder 72/14)
  - Musicians' Symphony Orchestra, N.Y. (Box-folder 72/15)
  - Muzzey, Anna (Box-folder 72/16)
  - "My" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 72/17)
  - Myers, C. H. (Box-folder 72/18)
  - "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 72/19)
  - "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 72/20)
  - NAACP see National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - Nabokov, Nicolas (telegram only) (Box-folder 72/21)
  - Nabokov, Nicolas (Box-folder 72/22)
  - Nachèz, Tivadar (Box-folder 72/23)
  - Naples, Italy. Hotels (Box-folder 72/24)
  - Napolitano, Franco (Box-folder 72/25)
  - Narodny, Ivan (Box-folder 72/26)
  - Nathan, Hans (letters to only) (Box-folder 72/28)
  - The Nation (Box-folder 72/27)
  - "National A" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 72/29)
  - National Association for American Composers and Conductors see also Hadley, Henry and Mrs. (Box-folder 72/30)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box-folder 72/31)
  - National Association of Amateur Chamber Music Players (Box-folder 72/32)
  - National Broadcasting Company (including N.B.C. Artists Service). Illingworth, Elsie (Box-folder 72/33)
  - National Broadcasting Company (including N.B.C. Artists Service). Koons, Walter (Box-folder 72/34)
  - National Broadcasting Company (including N.B.C. Artists Service). La Prade, Ernest (Box-folder 72/35)
  - National Broadcasting Company (including N.B.C. Artists Service). Levine, Marks, 1927-1935 (Box-folder 72/36)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Levine, Marks, 1936 (Box-folder 72/37)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Levine, Marks, 1937 (Box-folder 72/38)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Levine, Marks, 1938 (Box-folder 72/39)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Levine, Marks, 1939 (Box-folder 72/40)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Meyer, Dorothy (Box-folder 72/41)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Pottenger, Cleone (Box-folder 72/42)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Miscellany (Box-folder 72/43)
  - National Cathedral (Box-folder 72/44)
  - National Concert and Artists Corporation (Box-folder 72/45)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box-folder 72/46)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties (Box-folder 72/47)
  - National Federation of Music Clubs (Box-folder 72/48)
  - "National G" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 73/1)
  - National Gallery of Art (U.S.) (Box-folder 73/2)
  - National Music Council (Box-folder 73/3)
  - National Negro Memorial (Box-folder 73/4)
  - National String Quartet (Box-folder 73/5)
  - National Symphony Orchestra see also Kindler, Hans (Box-folder 73/6)
  - "Nau" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 73/7)
  - NBC see National Broadcasting Company
  - "Ne" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 73/8)
  - Neblett, Leona (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Neeter, Philip (Box-folder 73/10)
  - Neher, Edna (Box-folder 73/11)
  - Neighborhood Music School (Box-folder 73/12)
  - Neill, Lucy H. (Box-folder 73/13)
  - Neill-Skolnik, Amy (Box-folder 73/14)
  - Neumann, Agnes (Box-folder 73/15)
  - Nevin, Ethelbert, Mrs. (Box-folder 73/16)
  - "New A--Z" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 73/17)
  - New England Conservatory of Music, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 73/18)
  - New England Conservatory of Music, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 73/19)
  - New England Conservatory of Music, undated (Box-folder 73/20)
  - New Haven. Civic Orchestra Association (Box-folder 73/21)
  - New Haven hotels, etc. (Box-folder 73/23)
  - New Haven Symphony Orchestra (Box-folder 73/22)
  - New Jersey College for Women (Box-folder 73/24)
  - New Music String Quartet (Box-folder 73/25)
  - New School for Social Research (Box-folder 73/26)
  - New York. Banks. Central Union Trust Company (Box-folder 73/29)
  - New York. Banks. Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company, 1929-1934 (Box-folder 73/30)
  - New York. Banks. Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company, 1935-1949 (Box-folder 73/31)
  - New York. Banks. Guaranty Trust Company, 1926-1934 (Box-folder 73/32)
  - New York. Banks. Guaranty Trust Company, 1935-1946, undated (Box-folder 73/33)
  - New York Brass Ensemble (Box-folder 73/34)
  - New York Chamber Music Society (Box-folder 73/35)
  - New York City. "A" miscellaneous see also "New A--Z" miscellaneous (Box-folder 73/27)
  - New York City. Officials (Box-folder 73/28)
  - New York City Symphony Orchestra (Box-folder 73/36)
  - New York. "Co" miscellaneous see also "New A--Z" miscellaneous (Box-folder 74/1)
  - New York. Colony Club, 1922-1929 (Box-folder 74/2)
  - New York. Colony Club, 1930-1935 (Box-folder 74/3)
  - New York. Colony Club, 1936-1941, undated (Box-folder 74/4)
  - New York. Cosmopolitan Club (Box-folder 74/5)
  - New York. Hotels (Box-folder 74/6)
  - New York. Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box-folder 74/7)
  - New York. Municipal Broadcasting System (Box-folder 74/8)
  - New York. Neighborhood Music School (Box-folder 74/9)
  - New York. "P" miscellaneous see also "New A--Z" miscellaneous (Box-folder 74/10)
  - New York. People's Institute (Box-folder 74/11)
  - New York Philharmonic-Symphony Orchestra (Box-folder 74/12)
  - New York Public Library, 1922-1936 (Box-folder 74/13)
  - New York Public Library, 1937 (Box-folder 74/14)
  - New York Public Library, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 74/15)
  - New York Public Library, 1941-1951, undated (Box-folder 74/16)
  - New York. Schola Cantorum see also Schola Cantorum, N.Y. (Box-folder 74/17)
  - New York State (Box-folder 74/24)
  - New York String Quartet (Box-folder 74/18)
  - New York Times see also Downes, Olin (Box-folder 74/19)
  - New York. Town Hall (Box-folder 74/20)
  - New York Trio (Box-folder 74/21)
  - New York University (Box-folder 74/22)
  - New York Worlds Fair (1939-1940) (Box-folder 74/23)
  - "Newa" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 74/25)
  - Newberry Library see Chicago. Newberry Library
  - Newell, Bernice E. (Box-folder 74/26)
  - Newman, Dolores M. (Box-folder 74/27)
  - Newman, Ernest (Box-folder 74/28)
  - Newmann, Josef (Box-folder 74/29)
  - Newsome, Nora (Box-folder 74/30)
  - Newton, Elbert (Box-folder 74/31)
  - Newton, Massachusetts. All-Newton Music School (Box-folder 74/32)
  - "Ni" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 74/33)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold (fund-raising letters) (Box-folder 74/34)
  - Nieland, Mischa (Box-folder 74/35)
  - Nies-Berger, Edouard (Box-folder 74/36)
  - Nikisch, Mitja (Box-folder 74/37)
  - Nin-Culmell, Joaquín (Box-folder 74/38)
  - "No" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 74/39)
  - Noble, Flora F. (Box-folder 74/40)
  - Noble, Horace T. see Musical America
  - Noblet, Malvina (Box-folder 74/41)
  - Noguchi, Isamu (Box-folder 74/42)
  - Noland, Maxwell, Mrs. (Box-folder 74/43)
  - "Nor" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 75/1)
  - Norfleet, Helen (Box-folder 75/2)
  - Norman, Toto (Box-folder 75/3)
  - Norris, Mary Dixon (Box-folder 75/4)
  - North, Gladys, 1917-1939 see also Littlehales, Lillian (Box-folder 75/5)
  - North, Gladys, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 75/6)
  - North, Gladys, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 75/7)
  - North, Gladys, undated (Box-folder 75/8)
  - North, Stanley (Box-folder 75/9)
  - North Carolina College at Durham (Box-folder 75/10)
  - North Carolina. University (Box-folder 75/11)
  - Northern Trust Company see Chicago. Northern Trust Company
  - Northwestern University (Box-folder 75/12)
  - Norton, Mae see O'Farrell, Mae Norton
  - Norton, Mary Dows Herter see Herter Norton, Mary Dows
  - Notley, Norman (Box-folder 75/13)
  - Nourse, Annie Endicott (Box-folder 75/14)
  - Novák, Jaroslav see Czechoslovakia
  - Novak, Sylvain (Box-folder 75/15)
  - Novelli, Michele (Box-folder 75/16)
  - "Nu" miscellaneous see also "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 75/17)
  - "O" miscellaneous (Box-folder 75/18)
  - Oakland, California (Box-folder 75/19)
  - Oakland Forum (Box-folder 75/20)
  - Oberndorfer, Marx E. (Box-folder 75/21)
  - Occidental College. Bird, Remsen, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 75/22)
  - Occidental College. Bird, Remsen, 1940-1945, undated (Box-folder 75/23)
  - Occidental College. Swan, Howard (Box-folder 75/24)
  - Occidental College. Miscellany (Box-folder 75/25)
  - Ochs, Erich (Box-folder 75/26)
  - Ocko, Bernard (Box-folder 75/27)
  - O'Farrell, Mae Norton (Box-folder 75/28)
  - Ohler, Friede Hoffmann (Box-folder 75/29)
  - Ojai, California (Box-folder 75/30)
  - Olmsted, Fannie M. (Box-folder 75/31)
  - "On-Ox" miscellaneous see also "O" miscellaneous (Box-folder 76/1)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 76/2)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1930-1932 (Box-folder 76/3)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1933 (Box-folder 76/4)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1934 (Box-folder 76/5)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1935 (Box-folder 76/6)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1936 (Box-folder 76/7)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1937 (Box-folder 76/8)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1938 (Box-folder 76/9)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1939 (Box-folder 76/10)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1940 (Box-folder 76/11)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 76/12)
  - Onnou, Alphonse and Jeanne, undated (Box-folder 76/13)
  - Opdycke, Mary Ellis (Box-folder 76/14)
  - Open Road, Inc. (Box-folder 76/15)
  - Organ Institute (Box-folder 76/16)
  - Ormandy, Eugene (Box-folder 76/17)
  - Ornstein, Leo (Box-folder 76/18)
  - Ortega, Ricardo, 1936 (Box-folder 76/19)
  - Ortega, Ricardo, 1937 (Box-folder 76/20)
  - Ortmann, Otto see Peabody Institute
  - Osgood, H. O. (Box-folder 76/21)
  - Ostrowska, Djina (Box-folder 76/22)
  - Oswald, Alfredo (Box-folder 76/23)
  - Otis, Philo Adams (Box-folder 76/24)
  - Otterstein, Adolph see San Jose State College
  - Overmyer, Grace (Box-folder 76/25)
  - Oxford University Press (Box-folder 76/26)
  - "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 77/1)
  - Pacific University (Box-folder 77/2)
  - Pacquet, Georges (Box-folder 77/3)
  - Paddock, Brace Whitman, Mrs. (Box-folder 77/4)
  - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan and Mrs. (Box-folder 77/5)
  - Paganini Quartet (Box-folder 77/6)
  - Pagano, Carl (Box-folder 77/7)
  - Page, Marian H. (Box-folder 77/8)
  - Page, Ruth (Box-folder 77/9)
  - Page, Willis (Box-folder 77/10)
  - Painlevé, Paul (Box-folder 77/11)
  - Palestine Conservatoire of Music in Jerusalem (Box-folder 77/12)
  - Palm Springs, California (Box-folder 77/13)
  - Palmgren, Selim (Box-folder 77/14)
  - "Pan-Pas" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 77/15)
  - Pan American Union (Box-folder 77/16)
  - Pappoutsakis, James (Box-folder 77/17)
  - Paravox Hearing Aids (Box-folder 77/18)
  - Paris. Ecole normale de musique (Box-folder 77/19)
  - Paris, France. Hotels (Box-folder 77/20)
  - Park, Marion Edwards (Box-folder 77/21)
  - Parker, Henry Taylor (Box-folder 77/22)
  - Parker, Horatio (Box-folder 77/23)
  - Parker, Katharine B. (Box-folder 77/24)
  - Parlow, Kathleen, circa 1925-1934 (Box-folder 77/25)
  - Parlow, Kathleen, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 77/26)
  - Parlow, Kathleen, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 77/27)
  - Parlow, Kathleen, 1940-1950 (Box-folder 77/28)
  - Parlow, Kathleen, undated (Box-folder 77/29)
  - Parmelee, James (Box-folder 77/30)
  - Partch, Harry (Box-folder 77/31)
  - Pasadena Music Festival Association and Pasadena Civic Orchestra Association (Box-folder 77/32)
  - Pascal, Vincent de (Box-folder 77/33)
  - Pasquale, Joseph de see also De Pasquale, Joseph and Maria (Box-folder 77/34)
  - "Pat-Pay" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 78/1)
  - Patterson, Alfred Nash see Boston. Chorus Pro Musica
  - Patterson, Arthur C. (Box-folder 78/2)
  - Pattison, Lee (Box-folder 78/3)
  - Paul, Irene see Dean Paul, Irene
  - Payne, Walter A. (Box-folder 78/4)
  - Pazmor, Radiana (Box-folder 78/5)
  - "Pe" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 78/6)
  - Peabody Conservatory (Box-folder 78/7)
  - Peabody Institute (Box-folder 78/8)
  - Peaslee, Clifford (Box-folder 78/9)
  - Peirce, Elizabeth (Box-folder 78/10)
  - Peixotto, Ernest (Box-folder 78/11)
  - Pelényi, John and Mrs. (Box-folder 78/12)
  - Pendleton, Ellen see Wellesley College. Pendleton, Ellen
  - Penha, Michael (Box-folder 78/13)
  - Penniman, Gwendolen Brooks (Box-folder 78/14)
  - Pennington, John and Alice (Box-folder 78/15)
  - People's Institute see New York. People's Institute
  - People's Symphony Concerts (Box-folder 78/16)
  - Pepper, Jack and Dede (Box-folder 78/17)
  - "Per" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 78/18)
  - Perelman, Dora (Box-folder 78/19)
  - Perera, Lionello and Carolyn (Box-folder 78/20)
  - Perk, Edna S. (Box-folder 78/21)
  - Perkins, Francis D. (Box-folder 78/22)
  - Pernel, Orrea (Box-folder 78/23)
  - Perrier, P. (Box-folder 78/24)
  - Perry, C.H. and E.R. (Box-folder 78/25)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton (Box-folder 78/26)
  - Persinger, Louis, 1925-1928 (Box-folder 78/27)
  - Persinger, Louis, 1932-1937, undated (Box-folder 78/28)
  - Pessl, Yella (Box-folder 78/29)
  - Peter, Madame Marc (Box-folder 78/30)
  - Peterson, Anna (Box-folder 78/31)
  - Petit, Raymond (Box-folder 78/32)
  - Petre, Thomas (Box-folder 78/33)
  - Petri, Egon (Box-folder 78/34)
  - Petroff, F. N. (Box-folder 78/35)
  - Petrovic, B. (Box-folder 78/36)
  - Pettis, Ashley (Box-folder 78/37)
  - Peyser, Ethel R. (Box-folder 78/38)
  - Pezzé-Pascolato, Maria (Box-folder 78/39)
  - Pezzi, Anna Poltronieri (Box-folder 78/40)
  - Pfatteicher, Carl F. (Box-folder 78/41)
  - "Ph" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 79/1)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance (Box-folder 79/2)
  - Philadelphia. Matinée Musical Club (Box-folder 79/3)
  - Philadelphia Orchestra (Box-folder 79/4)
  - Philadelphia. Miscellany (Box-folder 79/5)
  - Philipp, Isidor (Box-folder 79/6)
  - Philippines. Boy Scouts of Cagayan Valley College see Boy Scouts of America, Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Troop and Cagayan Valley College
  - Phillips, William (Box-folder 79/7)
  - Phillips Memorial Gallery (Box-folder 79/8)
  - "Pi" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 79/9)
  - Pierce, Edwin Hall (Box-folder 79/10)
  - Piastro, Mishel (Box-folder 79/11)
  - Pickman, Edward M. (Box-folder 79/12)
  - Pierce, Mabel (Box-folder 79/13)
  - Pierné, Gabriel (Box-folder 79/14)
  - Pilati, Mario (Box-folder 79/15)
  - Piller, Boaz (Box-folder 79/16)
  - Pillois, Jacques and Marthe (Box-folder 79/17)
  - Piney Woods Country Life School (Box-folder 79/18)
  - Pini, Anthony (Box-folder 79/19)
  - Pipes, Susie Fennell (Box-folder 79/20)
  - Pisk, Paul Amadeus (Box-folder 79/21)
  - Piston, Walter (Box-folder 79/22)
  - "Pit" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 79/23)
  - Pitluck, Sherman F. (Box-folder 79/24)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Banks (Box-folder 79/25)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Berkshire Evening Eagle see also Berkshire Evening Eagle (Box-folder 79/26)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Boys' Club (Box-folder 79/27)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Chamber of Commerce (Box-folder 79/28)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. City Government (Box-folder 79/29)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Community Music School (Box-folder 79/30)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Community Music School. Crane, Winnie Davis (Box-folder 79/31)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Community Music School. Minutes, etc. (Box-folder 79/32)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Hotels (Box-folder 79/33)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Library see Berkshire Athenaeum
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Pittsfield Anti-Tuberculosis Association (Box-folder 79/34)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Pittsfield Anti-Tuberculosis Association Gift, 1915 (Box-folder 79/35)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Women's Club (Box-folder 79/36)
  - Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Miscellany (Box-folder 79/37)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 79/38)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 79/39)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 79/40)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1932 (Box-folder 79/41)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1933 (Box-folder 79/42)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 79/43)
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, undated (Box-folder 79/44)
  - "Pl" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 80/1)
  - Platt, Charles A. (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Playhouse in the Hills (Box-folder 80/3)
  - Plochmann, George (Box-folder 80/4)
  - Plowitz, Theodor (Box-folder 80/5)
  - Plunkett, Thomas F. (Box-folder 80/6)
  - "Po" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 80/7)
  - Pochon, Alfred and Susan, 1916-1927 (Box-folder 80/8)
  - Pochon, Alfred and Susan, 1928-1947, undated (Box-folder 80/9)
  - Polak, Charlotte N. (Box-folder 80/10)
  - Polnauer, Josef (Box-folder 80/11)
  - Poltronieri, Alberto (Box-folder 80/12)
  - Pomona College. Edmunds, Charles K., 1930-1931 (Box-folder 80/13)
  - Pomona College. Edmunds, Charles K., 1932-1936 (Box-folder 80/14)
  - Pomona College. Edmunds, Charles K., 1937-1940, undated (Box-folder 80/15)
  - Pomona College. Lyman, Ralph H. (Box-folder 80/16)
  - Pomona College. Miscellany (Box-folder 80/17)
  - Pompa, Elizabeth (Box-folder 80/18)
  - Poore, Charles (Box-folder 80/19)
  - Poot, Marcel (Box-folder 80/20)
  - Poppe, Vera (Box-folder 80/21)
  - Popper, William see California. University. Berkeley. Popper, William
  - Porter, Hugh (Box-folder 80/22)
  - Porter, Lucy (Mrs. A. Kingsley Porter) (Box-folder 80/23)
  - Porter, Quincy and Mrs. (Box-folder 80/24)
  - Portland Symphony Society (Portland, Or.) (Box-folder 80/25)
  - Posell, Elsa (Box-folder 80/26)
  - Posselt, Ruth (Box-folder 80/27)
  - Postal Telegraph Co. (Box-folder 80/28)
  - Pottenger, Cleone see National Broadcasting Company. Pottenger, Cleone
  - Potter, Edward C. (Box-folder 80/29)
  - Poulenc, Francis (Box-folder 80/30)
  - Poulet, Gaston (Box-folder 80/31)
  - Power, Charles W. see South Mountain Association
  - Powell, John, Foundation (Box-folder 80/32)
  - Powell, Maud (Box-folder 80/33)
  - Power, Pomeroy W. (Box-folder 80/34)
  - "Pra" miscellaneous see also "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 80/35)
  - Prague (Box-folder 80/36)